clickenabler.com 2017-06-04

# Privacy policy - Biddly

**Thank you for visiting our website. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site.**

Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

**Collection of information**  
We collect personally identifiable information, like names, telephone numbers, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by visitors on our contact page. The information you provide is used to fulfil your specific request, usually concerning the supply of further information about our services and the costs associated with these services. This information is used to fulfil your specific request and is also then added to our mailing list.

**Cookie/tracking technology**  
The Site may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customise the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information.

**Distribution of information**  
We do not share the private information submitted on this website externally unless we are required to do by law.

**Commitment to data security**  
Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only officers of Biddly have access to this information.

**Privacy contact information**  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us.

**We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.**
